Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 26 Oct. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 26 Oct. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 26 Oct. 1973 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Clemson (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 26 Oct. 1973 (Carton 14)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 15 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Clemson (6 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 26 Oct. 1973 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 17 Nov. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 17 Nov. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 17 Nov. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 17 Nov. 1973 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 8 Sept. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 8 Sept. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense, Coaches' Copy], 8 Sept. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense, Coaches' Copy], 8 Sept. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Georgia (1 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 29 Sept. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Georgia (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 29 Sept. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Georgia (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 29 Sept. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Georgia (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 29 Sept. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Georgia (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense, Coaches' Copy], 29 Sept. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Georgia (6 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense, Coaches' Copy], 29 Sept. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Kansas (Liberty Bowl) (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 17 Dec. 1973 (Carton 15)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 15 minutes, 30 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Kansas (Liberty Bowl) (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 17 Dec. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Kansas (Liberty Bowl) (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 17 Dec. 1973 (Carton 15)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 18 minutes, 30 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Kansas (Liberty Bowl) (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 17 Dec. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 13 Oct. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 13 Oct. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense, Coaches' Copy], 13 Oct. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense, Coaches' Copy], 13 Oct 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 13 Oct. 1973 (Carton 16)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 14 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Maryland (6 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 13 Oct. 1973 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Nebraska (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 22 Sept. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Nebraska (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 22 Sept. 1973 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. Nebraska (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 22 Sept. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Nebraska (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 22 Sept. 1973 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. Penn State (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as Reel 1], 10 Nov. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Penn State (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as Reel 2], 10 Nov. 1973 (Carton 16)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 18 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Penn State (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as Reel 3], 10 Nov. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Penn State (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as Reel 4], 10 Nov. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Penn State (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 10 Nov. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Penn State (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 10 Nov. 1973 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. Penn State (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 10 Nov. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Penn State (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 10 Nov. 1973 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. Penn State (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half defense], 10 Nov. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Penn State (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half defense], 10 Nov. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (1 of 3) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 3 Nov. 1973 (Carton 16)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 17 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. South Carolina (2 of 3) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 3 Nov. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (3 of 3) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 3 Nov. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 2) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 6 Oct. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 2) [labeled on canister as Kicking Game], 6 Oct. 1973 (Carton 16)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 14 minutes, 30 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 5) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 15 Sept. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 5) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 15 Sept. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 5) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 15 Sept. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 5) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense, Coaches' Copy], 15 Sept. 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Virginia (5 of 5) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 15 Sept. 1973 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 24 Nov. 1973 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 24 Nov. 1973 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 24 Nov. 1973 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 24 Nov. 1973 (Carton 17)
- Red/White game (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 1973 (Carton 16)
- Red/White game (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 1973 (Carton 16)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 13 minutes, 45 seconds; color; no sound
- Red/White game (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 1973 (Carton 16)
- Red/White game (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 1973 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 16 Nov. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 16 Nov. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 16 Nov. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 16 Nov. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 1), 16 Nov. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 2), 16 Nov. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 1), 16 Nov. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 2), 16 Nov. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 21 Sept. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 21 Sept. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 21 Sept. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 21 Sept. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Clemson (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 21 Sept. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Clemson (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 21 Sept. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Clemson (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 21 Sept. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Clemson (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 21 Sept. 1974 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. Clemson (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 21 Sept. 1974 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Clemson (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 21 Sept. 1974 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 14 Sept. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 14 Sept. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 14 Sept. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 14 Sept. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 14 Sept. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 14 Sept. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 14 Sept. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 14 Sept. 1974 (Carton 92)
- NC State vs. Duke (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 14 Sept. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 14 Sept. 1974 (Carton 92)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 5 Oct. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 5 Oct. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 5 Oct. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 5 Oct. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 5 Oct. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 5 Oct. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 1), 5 Oct. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 2), 5 Oct. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 1), 5 Oct. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 2), 5 Oct. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Houston (Astro-Blue Bonnet Bowl) (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 23 Dec. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Houston (Astro-Blue Bonnet Bowl) (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 23 Dec. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Houston (Astro-Blue Bonnet Bowl) (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 23 Dec. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Houston (Astro-Blue Bonnet Bowl) (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 23 Dec. 1974 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 26 Oct. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 26 Oct. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 26 Oct. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 26 Oct. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense 1 of 2], 26 Oct. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Maryland (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as Offense 2 of 2], 26 Oct. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Maryland (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Defense 1 of 2], 26 Oct. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Maryland (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Defense 2 of 2], 26 Oct. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Penn State (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 9 Nov. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Penn State (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 9 Nov. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Penn State (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 9 Nov. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Penn State (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 9 Nov. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Penn State (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 1), 9 Nov. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Penn State (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 2), 9 Nov. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Penn State (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 1), 9 Nov. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Penn State (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 2), 9 Nov. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 2 Nov. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 2 Nov. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 2 Nov. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 2 Nov. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 2 Nov. 1974 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 2 Nov. 1974 (Carton 20)
  16mm film; Approximate runtimes: 12 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. South Carolina (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 1), 2 Nov. 1974 (Carton 20)
  16mm film; Approximate runtimes: 13 minutes, 45 seconds; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. South Carolina (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 2), 2 Nov. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 1), 2 Nov. 1974 (Carton 20)
  16mm film; Approximate runtimes: 14 minutes, 30 seconds; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. South Carolina (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 2), 2 Nov. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. South Carolina - 2nd Half Defense, 2 Nov 1974 (Carton 20)
  Researchers may request copies of digital files. The Special Collections Research Center cannot guarantee that all files will open and will not in all cases have software available to read files.
  DVD
- NC State vs. Syracuse (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 28 Sept. 1974 (Carton 20)
  16mm film; Approximate runtimes: 8 minutes; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Syracuse (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 28 Sept. 1974 (Carton 20)
  16mm film; Approximate runtimes: 13 minutes, 45 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Syracuse (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 28 Sept. 1974 (Carton 20)
  16mm film; Approximate runtimes: 10 minutes, 30 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Syracuse (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 28 Sept. 1974 (Carton 20)
  16mm film; Approximate runtimes: 11 minutes; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Syracuse (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 28 Sept. 1974 (Carton 20)
  16mm film; Approximate runtimes: 11 minutes; black white; no sound
- NC State vs. Syracuse (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 28 Sept. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. Syracuse (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 28 Sept. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. Syracuse (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 28 Sept. 1974 (Carton 93)
- NC State vs. Syracuse (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 28 Sept. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. Syracuse (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 28 Sept. 1974 (Carton 94)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 19 Oct. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 19 Oct. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 19 Oct. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 19 Oct. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 19 Oct. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 19 Oct. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 1), 19 Oct. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 2), 19 Oct. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 1), 19 Oct. 1974 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 2), 19 Oct. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 12 Oct. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 12 Oct. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 12 Oct. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 12 Oct. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Virginia (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 12 Oct. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Virginia (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 12 Oct. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Virginia (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 1), 12 Oct. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Virginia (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (copy 2), 12 Oct. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Virginia (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 1), 12 Oct. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Virginia (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (copy 2), 12 Oct. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 7 Sept. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 7 Sept. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 7 Sept. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 7 Sept. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 7 Sept. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 7 Sept. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 7 Sept. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 7 Sept. 1974 (Carton 94)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 7 Sept. 1974 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 7 Sept. 1974 (Carton 94)
- Red/White game (1 of 3) [labeled on canister as 1 of 3], 13 Apr. 1974 (Carton 19)
- Red/White game (2 of 3) [labeled on canister as 2 of 3], 13 Apr. 1974 (Carton 19)
- Red/White game (3 of 3) [labeled on canister as 3 of 3], 13 Apr. 1974 (Carton 19)
- Highlights, 1974 (Carton 21)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 41 minutes, 30 seconds; color; no sound
- Highlights (NC State vs. Clemson, Arizona State), 1974 (Carton 25)
  Television broadcast film; Approximate runtime: 2 minutes; color; sound
- Offense, 24 Aug. 1974 (Carton 21)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 1 minute; color; sound
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 4) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 25 Oct. 1975 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 4) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 25 Oct. 1975 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 4) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 25 Oct. 1975 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 4) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 25 Oct. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as Offense 1 of 2], 15 Nov. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as Offense 2 of 2], 15 Nov. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as Defense 1 of 2] (copy 1), 15 Nov. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as Defense 1 of 2] (copy 2), 15 Nov. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Duke (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 15 Nov. 1975 (Carton 92)
- NC State vs. Duke (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as Defense 2 of 2] (copy 1), 15 Nov. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Duke (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as Defense 2 of 2] (copy 2), 15 Nov. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Duke (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 15 Nov. 1975 (Carton 94)
- NC State Junior Varsity vs. Duke Junior Varsity (9 of 9), 14 Nov. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 6 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 6 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 6 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 6 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 6 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 6 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 6 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 6 Sept. 1975 (Carton 94)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 6 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Florida (1 of 7) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 20 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Florida (2 of 7) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 20 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Florida (3 of 7) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 20 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Florida (4 of 7) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 20 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Florida (5 of 7) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 20 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Florida (6 of 7) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 20 Sept. 1975 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Florida (7 of 7) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 20 Sept. 1975 (Carton 23)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 4 minutes, 30 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Indiana (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st Quarter], 4 Oct. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Indiana (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd Quarter], 4 Oct. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Indiana (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 3rd Quarter], 4 Oct. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Indiana (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 4th Quarter], 4 Oct. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Indiana (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 4 Oct. 1975 (Carton 94)
- NC State vs. Indiana (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 4 Oct. 1975 (Carton 94)
- NC State vs. Indiana (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 4 Oct. 1975 (Carton 94)
- NC State vs. Indiana (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 4 Oct. 1975 (Carton 94)
- NC State vs. Indiana (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 4 Oct. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Indiana (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 4 Oct. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 7) [labeled on canister as 1 of 4], 11 Oct. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 7) [labeled on canister as 2 of 4], 11 Oct. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 7) [labeled on canister as 3 of 4], 11 Oct. 1975 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 7) [labeled on canister as 4 of 4], 11 Oct. 1975 (Carton 23)